Finding Aid for the Adeline Levine Love Canal Collection, 1893-1995 (bulk 1978-1995)
Buffalo History Museum. Research Library
- Citizens Groups, V.
  - Love Canal Homeowners Association, V.A.
    - LCHA/Gibbs correspondence, September 1978-August 6, 1979 (Box-folder 16.6)
    - LCHA/Gibbs correspondence, August 10-December 1979 (Box-folder 16.7)
    - LCHA/Gibbs correspondence, January-July 1980 (Box-folder 17.1)
    - LCHA/Gibbs correspondence, August-December 1980, June-July, November 1981 (Box-folder 17.2)
    - LCHA/Gibbs and United Way, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 17.3)
  - Citizen's Clearinghouse for Hazardous Wastes, Inc., V.B.
    - Citizen's Clearinghouse for Hazardous Wastes, Inc. (CCHN). Constitution and bylaws, articles of incorporation, minutes ( December 27, 1983 and April 13, 1984), reports, financial statements (Box-folder 17.4)
    - CCHW correspondence, 1981-1988 (Box-folder 17.5)
    - CCHW Action Bulletin, no. 1-8, 12, 13, 15, 18, 19, 21 ( 1983-1989) (Box-folder 17.6)
    - CCHW Everyone's Backyard (Quarterly), v. 1-3, 4(2)-5(2), 6(2), 7(2) ( 1982-1989) (Box-folder 17.7)
    - Manuals. "Experts: A User's Guide" ( 1985) and "Environmental Testing??" ( undated) (Box-folder 18.1)
    - CCHW manuals (drafts). "How Important Are Community Organizations and Can Citizens Really Fight Major Corporations and Government?" and untitled (law). (Box-folder 18.2)
    - CCHN. Gibbs speech, "Impacts of Environmental Disasters on Communities," April 13, 1985; press release, March 1, 1985; catalog of publications and materials; publication, Love Canal: A Chronology of Events that Shaped a Movement, 1984 (Box-folder 18.3)
    - CCHN. Health survey questionnaires; internship program information (Box-folder 18.4)
  - Various, V.C.
    - Ecumenical Task-Force (ETF). Information and Progress Report, November 12, 1979 (Box-folder 18.5)
    - ETF. Reports, March 20, 1979-August 1, 1980; August 1, 1980-January 31, 1981; June 23, 1983 (Box-folder 18.6)
    - Environmental Defense Fund (EDF), guidelines for public participation in Superfund programs, 1982 (Box-folder 18.7)
    - Other grass roots organizations and environmental newsletters (Box-folder 18.8)
- Hooker and Chemical Manufacturers Association, VI.
  - Hooker. Includes Levine notes, correspondence, deed, clippings, Occidental/Hooker financial statements, miscellaneous (Box-folder 19.1)
  - Hooker. Factline, n. 1-13; "Chemical Fact File"; Oxy Today, n. 9 ( 1977) (Box-folder 19.2)
  - Hooker. Thomas. Salt and Water, Power and People, 1955; "The Other Side of Love Canal," 1980; Zeusse, "Love Canal: The Truth Seeps Out," 1981 (Box-folder 19.3)
  - Hooker. Urban Development Corporation (UDC) deal, 1980 (Box-folder 19.4)
  - Hooker. Sultz report, 1983 (Box-folder 19.5)
  - Chemical Manufacturers Association (CMA), pamphlets and advertisements (Box-folder 19.6)
  - CMA, information on dioxin (Box-folder 19.7)
- Niagara Falls and William Love, VII.
  - Niagara Falls census information (Box-folder 19.8)
  - Niagara Falls Board of Education materials (Box-folder 19.9)
  - Deed for Love Canal land, Hooker to Niagara Falls Board of Education (Box-folder 19.10)
  - William Love and a Model City in Lewiston, N.Y. Parry; "William T. Love and the Development of a Model City," 1976; Description and Plan of the Model City Located at Lewiston, Niagara County, N.Y. Chartered by Special Act of the New York Legislature, Designed to be the Most Perfect City in Existence. Lewiston: The Model Town Co., 1893 (Box-folder 19.11)
  - Niagara Falls. Levine notes with City Engineers; clipping on gorge history, 1983 (Box-folder 19.12)
- Legal Aspects, VIII.
  VIII.A. Hearings
  VIII.B. Lawsuits
  VIII.C. Various
  - Hearings, VIII.A.
    - State. December 14, 1982 (Abrams) (Box-folder 20.1)
    - State. February 17, 1983 (Box-folder 20.2)
    - State. September 21, 1983 (Axelrod) (Box-folder 20.3)
    - State and congressional. Residents' testimonies. Gibbs, Hillis, McCoulf, Grenzy, Noak. (Box-folder 20.4)
    - Congressional. October 30, 1978 (Box-folder 20.5)
    - Congressional. March-June 1979 (Box-folder 20.6)
    - Hearings Congressional. March 21, 1979 (Paigen) (Box-folder 20.7)
    - Congressional, March 27, 1979 (LaFalce) (Box-folder 20.8)
    - Congressional. May 22, 1980 (Box-folder 21.1)
    - Congressional, March 31, 1982 (Florio) (Box-folder 21.2)
    - Congressional. August 9, 1982 (Box-folder 21.3)
    - Hinchey, Pillittere, et. al. Bill, May 1983, "Act to amend the environmental conservation law and the general municipal law, in relation to providing for certification of completion of the Love Canal remedial program..." (Box-folder 21.4)
    - LaFalce on Love Canal (press releases, correspondence) (Box-folder 21.5)
  - Lawsuits, VIII.B
    - US v. Hooker (four versions, undated) (Box-folder 21.6)
    - US v. Hooker. Hooker counterclaim, 1980; partial decision ( 1994); Levine notes; clippings (Box-folder 21.7)
    - Harry and Lois Gibbs v. City of Niagara Falls, et al., October 26, 1978 (Box-folder 21.8)
    - Stephen J. Mervak, et al. v. City of Niagara Falls, et al., 1979 (Box-folder 21.9)
    - Residents of Love Canal v. Hooker, 1980 (Box-folder 21.10)
  - Various, VIII.C.
    - ETF, CCHW, et al. Motion v. LCARA (Love Canal Area Revitalization Agency) (Box-folder 21.11)
    - House Resolutions 1048 and 1049, January 18, 1979 (Box-folder 21.12)
    - Executive Law, Section 10 (relocation) (Box-folder 21.13)
- Government Documents, IX.
  IX.A. Various
  IX.B. United States Environmental Protection Agency
  IX.C. New York State Department of Health
  - Various, IX.A.
    - NYSDOT. Love Canal Task Force (evacuation and relocation) (Box-folder 22.1)
    - NYS December Study and Clean Up Program Update. Love Canal Landfill, no. 1-9, 11, 14, 15, and January 1995 (unnumbered); Hyde Park Landfill, no. 6 (Box-folder 22.2)
  - United States Environmental Protection Agency, IX.B.
    - Costs of Love Canal, EPA, DOT, DOH, HHS, FEMA (Box-folder 22.3)
    - EPA. Brochure, "Everybody's Problem: Hazardous Waste," 1980 (Box-folder 22.4)
    - EPA. Materials received November 1981 re decisions made in Spring 1980 -- materials dated 1978-1979; US v. Hooker complaint (Box-folder 22.5)
    - EPA. Materials received November 1981 re decisions made in Spring 1980 -- materials dated March-May 17, 1980 (Box-folder 22.6)
    - EPA. Materials received Nov 1981 re decisions made in Spring 1980 -- materials dated May 19-October 8, 1980 (Box-folder 22.7)
    - EPA. Materials received by Gibbs, as per FOIA request, August 1982 -- materials dated February 22, 1980-July 28, 1982 (Box-folder 22.8)
    - EPA. Cooperative agreement with NYSDEC, July 1982 (Box-folder 22.9)
    - EPA. Materials, July 1982 ( Environmental Monitoring at Love Canal) (Box-folder 22.10)
    - EPA. Reactions to report. Environmental Monitoring at Love Canal, and congressional action, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 22.11)
    - EPA and NYSDOH. Report of Meetings Between Scientists from HEW and EPA, and Paigen and Scientists of NYSDOH Concerning Love Canal," July 1979 (Box-folder 23.1)
    - EPA and NYSDOH. Levine correspondence, January-March 1981; DOH materials dated November 1979, May-June 1980 (Box-folder 23.2)
  - New York State Department of Health, IX.C.
    - Materials dated April 25, 1978; August 2, 1978; February 8, 1979; August 13, 1979 (Box-folder 23.3)
    - Questionnaire (Vianna) (Box-folder 23.4)
    - Collected Documents, Tabs 1-8 (table of contents, tab 1) (Box-folder 23.5)
    - Collected Documents, Tabs 9-14 (Box-folder 23.6)
    - Collected Documents, Tabs 15-21 (Box-folder 23.7)
    - Collected Documents, Tabs 22-24 (Box-folder 23.8)
    - Collected Documents, Tabs 25-31A (Box-folder 24.1)
    - Collected Documents, Tabs 33-36 (Box-folder 24.2)
    - Collected Documents, Tabs 37-40 (Box-folder 24.3)
    - Collected Documents, Tabs 41-47 (Box-folder 24.4)
    - Collected Documents, Tabs 48-66 (Box-folder 24.5)
- Research and Reports, X.
  X.A. Center for Disease Control/SUNYAB Proposed Health Study, 1980
  X.B. Paigen, Beverly
  X.C. Reports
  X.D. Papers
  X.E. Articles
  X.F. Various
  - Center for Disease Control/SUNYAB Proposed Health Study, 1980, X.A.
    - Materials, August 20-September 22, 1980 (Box-folder 25.1)
    - Materials, October 3-October 23, 1980 (Box-folder 25.2)
    - Materials, October 24-November 7, 1980 (Box-folder 25.3)
    - Materials, November 11-November 24, 1980 (Box-folder 25.4)
    - Materials, December 10, 1980 and February 12, 1981 (Box-folder 25.5)
    - Budget (Box-folder 25.6)
    - Levine notes, clippings (Box-folder 25.7)
    - Prospectuses from other institutions to CDC (Box-folder 25.8)
  - Paigen, Beverly, X.B.
    - "Notebook Prepared for Roswell Park Memorial Institute Board of Visitors," March 7, 1980, Sections 1-23 (Box-folder 26.1)
    - "Notebook Prepared for Roswell Appendices 1-5 (Box-folder 26.2)
    - Studies, 1978-1983 (Box-folder 26.3)
    - Studies, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 26.4)
    - Studies, 1984-1988,undated (Box-folder 26.5)
    - Materials, October 1978-November 1980, July 1981 (Box-folder 26.6)
    - Nomination for AAAS Award for Scientific Freedom and Responsibility, 1981 (Box-folder 26.7)
  - Reports, X.C.
    - Policies and Poisons: The Containment of Long-Term Hazards to Human Health in the Environment and in the Workplace. Science Council of Canada Report No. 28, October 1977 (Box-folder 27.1)
    - Love Canal: Public Health Time Bomb: A Special Report to the Governor and Legislature. NYSDOH, Office of Public Health, September 1978 (Box-folder 27.2)
    - Ebert. "Comments on The Love Canal Pollution Abatement Plan", September 1978 (Box-folder 27.3)
    - Environmental Quality, the Ninth Annual Report of the Council on Environmental Quality, Chapter 4, "Toxic Substances," December 1978 (Box-folder 27.4)
    - Draft Report on Hazardous Waste Disposal in Erie And Niagara Counties, New York. Interagency Task Force on Hazardous Wastes, March 1979 (Box-folder 27.5)
    - Toxic Substances in New York's Environment: an Interim Report. NYSDEC and NYSDOH, May 1979 (Box-folder 27.6)
    - Long-Term Hazards of Polychlorinated Dibenzodioxins and Polychlorinated Dibenzofurans. IARC Internal Technical Report No. 78/001, June 1979 (Box-folder 27.7)
    - Industrial Hazardous Waste Generation in New York State: an Inventory. NYSDEC, June 1979 (Box-folder 27.8)
    - Hearings on: Inactive Hazardous Waste Disposal Sites and the Report of the Interagency Task Force on Hazardous Wastes. Interagency Task Force on Hazardous Wastes, NYSDEC, October 1979 (Box-folder 27.9)
    - Barron. "Report of Pilot Project: Nerve Conduction Determinations at Love Canal," January 1980 (Box-folder 27.10)
    - Report of the Subcommittee on the Potential Health Effects of Toxic Chemical Dumps of the DHEW Committee to Coordinate Environmental and Related Programs. HEW, February 1, 1980 (Box-folder 27.11)
    - Thomas Report, Report of the Governor's Panel to Review Scientific Studies and the Development of Public Policy on Problems Resulting From Hazardous Wastes, June 1980 (Box-folder 28.1)
    - Thomas Report. Dowling. "Materials distributed to the Thomas Panel on June 6, 1980." (Box-folder 28.2-28.3)
    - Thomas Report. Copy of executive order, June 4, 1980; lists of Sloan-Kettering Board members, Thomas Panel members; attendance record of Thomas Panel members (Box-folder 28.4)
    - Thomas Report. Correspondence. July 1978-June 1981 (Box-folder 28.5)
    - Thomas Report. Correspondence. FOIA requests, with information on FOIA, health laws, and public officers laws (Box-folder 28.6)
    - Thomas Report. Correspondence. National Academy of Science (Box-folder 28.7)
    - Thomas Report. Correspondence. Science (Box-folder 28.8)
    - Thomas Report. Articles by/about Thomas (Box-folder 28.9)
    - Thomas Report. Articles (Box-folder 28.10)
    - Bartosiewicz. 609...and counting: Hazardous Wastes and the Public's Health in New York State, Spring 1980 (Box-folder 29.1)
    - Vianna. Adverse Pregnancy Outcomes in the Love Canal Area. NYSDOH, April 1980 (Box-folder 29.2)
    - Reviews of Pilot Cytogenetic Study on Residents of Love Canal, May 1980 (Box-folder 29.3)
    - Hinchey Report, Preliminary Report of New York State Assembly Task Force on Toxic Substances: Inquiry into the Love Canal and Related Matters, May 29, 1980 (Box-folder 29.4)
    - The Remedial Construction Project at Love Canal, Niagara Falls, New York: Findings and Comments. Clement Associates for NYSDOT, August 1980 (Box-folder 29.5)
    - "..Assessment of the Threat to Public Health Posed by Toxic Chemicals in the United States," Surgeon General/HHS to US Senate, September 1980 (Box-folder 29.6)
    - Organic Chemicals and Drinking Water. NYSDOH, 1980? (Box-folder 29.7)
    - Shaw and Milbrath. Final Report on a Study of Citizen Participation in Governmental Decision Making with Respect to the Toxic Waste Threat at Love Canal, Niagara Falls, New York. EPA, January 1981 (Box-folder 29.8)
    - Cancer Mortality Trends, 1950-1975. New Jersey DEP, March 1981 (Box-folder 29.9)
    - Love Canal. A Special Report to the Governor and Legislature. NYSDOH, Office of Public Health, April 1981 (Box-folder 29.10)
    - Hazardous Waste Facilities with Interim Status May Be Endangering Public Health and the Environment. Comptroller General, GAO, September 1981 (Box-folder 30.1)
    - Health Effects of "Agent Orange" and Polychlorinated Dioxin Contaminants. AMA, October 1981 (Box-folder 30.2)
    - Overview of Environmental Pollution in the Niagara Frontier, New York. EPA, March 1982 (Box-folder 30.3)
    - Environmental Monitoring at Love Canal. EPA, May 1982 (Box-folder 30.4)
    - Love Canal: The Social Construction of a Disaster. FEMA, October 1982 (Box-folder 30.5)
    - A Study of Cytogenetic Patterns in Persons Living Near the Love Canal. CDC et al., May 1983 (Box-folder 30.6)
    - Health. "Assessment of Health Risks at Love Canal." CDC, May 1983 (Box-folder 30.7)
    - Siting of Hazardous Waste Landfills and Their Correlation with Racial and Economic Status of Surrounding Communities. GAO, June 1983 (Box-folder 30.8)
    - Habitability of the Love Canal Area: An Analysis of the Technical Basis for the Decision on the Habitability of the Emergency Declaration Area. OTA, June 1983 (Box-folder 31.1)
    - National Survey of Hazardous Waste Generators and Treatment, Storage, and Disposal Facilities Regulated under RCRA in 1981: Preliminary Highlights of Findings. EPA, August 1983 (Box-folder 31.2)
  - Papers, X.D.
    - Farrell. "Phases of Group Development." March 1979, Rice University (Box-folder 31.3)
    - Fisher. "Insurance Program for the Toxic Waste Dump Problem," 1979 (Box-folder 31.4)
    - Cornwell. "Organizations in a Disaster Setting: an Adversarial Model," July 1980 (Box-folder 31.5)
    - Masters. "Life Stage Responses to Environmental Crisis: the Case of the Love Canal, Niagara Falls, New York," August 20, 1980 (Box-folder 31.6)
    - Nazario. "Disaster Perpetrated by Man: A Call for Research Methodology for Investigation of Potential Effects of Toxic Waste Sites,: November 1980 (Box-folder 31.7)
    - Lester. "The Problems of Cleaning Up Uncontrolled Hazardous Waste Sites," Jan 3-8, 1981 (Box-folder 31.8)
    - Walsh. "A Micromobilization Process in a Non-Metropolitan Community: Middletown (Pa.) in the Wake of the TMI Accident," February 1981 (Box-folder 31.9)
    - Essays from the 11th Annual ATLA Environmental Law Essay Contest, 1981. Topic: "Love Canal et al.: The Federal Government's Rights, Responsibilities, and Liability for the Damage from Chemical Dumps." (Box-folder 31.10)
    - Beeson. "Criminal Enforcement at the EPA: a Review of the Past Year." November 1983, American Society of Criminology. (Box-folder 31.11)
    - Auerbach. "Sociology of Science,"undated (Box-folder 31.12)
    - Holt. "A Selective Review of Research on Health Effects of the Accident at Three Mile Island,"undated (Box-folder 31.13)
  - Articles, X.E.
    - General sociology (Box-folder 31.14)
    - Medical sociology, environmental health (Box-folder 32.1)
    - Sociology of science (Box-folder 32.2)
    - Science and ethics (Box-folder 32.3)
    - Whistle-blowing (Box-folder 32.4)
    - Science and politics, science and the law (Box-folder 32.5)
    - Science and politics. "Science Court" (Box-folder 32.6)
    - Science and politics. "Science Court," materials and correspondence (Box-folder 32.7)
    - Science and politics. "Science Court," Paigen-Havender Court, 1983 (Box-folder 32.8)
    - Science and politics. Picciano- Science suit correspondence (Box-folder 32.9)
    - Science and politics. Materials on suing Science (Box-folder 32.10)
    - Risk assessment (Box-folder 32.11)
    - Regulation and legislation (Box-folder 33.1)
    - Environmental pollution (Box-folder 33.2)
    - Toxic waste (Box-folder 33.3)
    - Materials compiled on hazardous wastes and community environmental health services (Box-folder 33.4)
    - Genetics and birth defects (Box-folder 33.5)
    - Cancer and carcinogens (Box-folder 33.6)
    - Dioxin (Box-folder 33.7)
    - Articles, Chemical testing (Box-folder 33.8)
    - Love Canal, Gibbs (Box-folder 33.9)
    - Paigen (Box-folder 33.10)
    - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 33.11)
  - Various, X.F.
    - Transcript. "Donahue," June 20, 1980 (Box-folder 33.12)
    - Transcript. "Nightline," May 21, 1981 (Box-folder 33.13)
    - Bibliographies. Abortion (Box-folder 33.14)
    - Bibliographies. Environmental movement (Box-folder 33.15)
    - Bibliographies. Love Canal ( 1979) (Box-folder 33.16)
    - Lists of publications. OSHA, June 1972; OTA, March 1983 (Box-folder 33.17)
- Photographs, negatives, and slides, XI.
  - Photographs, September 1978 (Box-folder 34.1)
  - Photographs, October 1978 (Box-folder 34.2)
  - Photographs, December 1978-1979 (Box-folder 34.3)
  - Photographs, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 34.4)
  - Photographs, 1983 (Box-folder 34.5)
  - Photographs, 1988-1989 and undated (Box-folder 34.6)
  - Negatives (Box-folder 34.7)
  - Slides. "Love Canal: The Issues and Controversies" (Box-folder 34.8)
  - Slides. "Primary set" (Box-folder 34.9)
  - Slides. "1-140" (Box-folder 35.1)
  - Slides. "Love Canal A-V she, with word slides" (Box-folder 35.2)
  - Slides. "Duplicates" (Box-folder 35.3)
  - Slides. Miscellaneous (Box-folder 35.4)
- Newspaper Clippings, XII.
  - undated (Box-folder 36.1)
  - January 1978 (Box-folder 36.2)
  - August 1-3, 1978 (Box-folder 36.3)
  - August 4, 1978 (Box-folder 36.4)
  - August 5-6, 1978 (Box-folder 36.5)
  - August 7-9, 1978 (Box-folder 36.6)
  - August 10-11, 1978 (Box-folder 36.7)
  - August 12-13, 1978 (Box-folder 36.8)
  - August 14-16, 1978 (Box-folder 36.9)
  - August 17-19, 1978 (Box-folder 36.10)
  - August 20-22, 1978 (Box-folder 36.11)
  - August 23-26, 1978 (Box-folder 36.12)
  - August 27-29, 1978 (Box-folder 36.13)
  - August 30-31, 1978 (Box-folder 36.14)
  - September 1-4, 1978 (Box-folder 36.15)
  - September 5-9, 1978 (Box-folder 36.16)
  - September 10-12, 1978 (Box-folder 36.17)
  - September 13-16, 1978 (Box-folder 36.18)
  - September 17-20, 1978 (Box-folder 36.19)
  - September 21-25, 1978 (Box-folder 36.20)
  - September 26-30, 1978 (Box-folder 36.21)
  - October 1-4, 1978 (Box-folder 36.22)
  - October 5-11, 1978 (Box-folder 36.23)
  - October 12-17, 1978 (Box-folder 36.24)
  - October 18-20, 1978 (Box-folder 36.25)
  - October 21-25, 1978 (Box-folder 36.26)
  - October 26-29, 1978 (Box-folder 36.27)
  - October 30-31, 1978 (Box-folder 36.28)
  - November 1-15, 1978 (Box-folder 36.29)
  - November 16-30, 1978 (Box-folder 36.30)
  - December 1-8, 1978 (Box-folder 37.1)
  - December 9-15, 1978 (Box-folder 37.2)
  - December 16-26, 1978 (Box-folder 37.3)
  - December 27-31, 1978 (Box-folder 37.4)
  - January 1-18, 1979 (Box-folder 37.5)
  - January 29-31, 1979 (Box-folder 37.6)
  - February 1-10, 1979 (Box-folder 37.7)
  - February 11-19, 1979 (Box-folder 37.8)
  - February 20-28, 1979 (Box-folder 37.9)
  - March 1-13, 1979 (Box-folder 37.10)
  - March 14-21, 1979 (Box-folder 37.11)
  - March 22-27, 1979 (Box-folder 37.12)
  - March 28-32, 1979 (Box-folder 37.13)
  - April 1-7, 1979 (Box-folder 37.14)
  - April 8-11, 1979 (Box-folder 37.15)
  - April 12-27, 1979 (Box-folder 37.16)
  - April 18-24, 1979 (Box-folder 37.17)
  - April 25-30, 1979 (Box-folder 37.18)
  - May 1-9, 1979 (Box-folder 37.19)
  - May 10-29, 1979 (Box-folder 37.20)
  - May 20-31, 1979 (Box-folder 38.1)
  - June 1-17, 1979 (Box-folder 38.2)
  - June 18-29, 1979 (Box-folder 38.3)
  - July 1979 (Box-folder 38.4)
  - August 1-21, 1979 (Box-folder 38.5)
  - August 22-31, 1979 (Box-folder 38.6)
  - September 1-9, 1979 (Box-folder 38.7)
  - September 10-17, 1979 (Box-folder 38.8)
  - September 18-30, 1979 (Box-folder 38.9)
  - October 1-24, 1979 (Box-folder 38.10)
  - October 15-19, 1979 (Box-folder 38.11)
  - October 20-31, 1979 (Box-folder 38.12)
  - November 1-8, 1979 (Box-folder 38.13)
  - November 9-18, 1979 (Box-folder 38.14)
  - November 19-30, 1979 (Box-folder 38.15)
  - December 1-10, 1979 (Box-folder 38.16)
  - December 11-18, 1979 (Box-folder 38.17)
  - December 19-31, 1979 (Box-folder 38.18)
  - January 1980 (Box-folder 39.1)
  - February 1980 (Box-folder 39.2)
  - March 1980 (Box-folder 39.3)
  - April 7-12, 1980 (Box-folder 39.5)
  - April 13-18, 1980 (Box-folder 39.6)
  - April 19-22, 1980 (Box-folder 39.7)
  - April 23-27, 1980 (Box-folder 39.8)
  - April 28-30, 1980 (Box-folder 39.9)
  - May 1-15, 1980 (Box-folder 39.10)
  - May 16, 1980 (Box-folder 39.11)
  - May 18, 1980 (Box-folder 39.12)
  - May 19, 1980 (Box-folder 39.13)
  - May 20, 1980 (Box-folder 39.14)
  - May 21, 1980 (Box-folder 39.15)
  - May 22, 1980 (Box-folder 39.16)
  - May 23-24, 1980 (Box-folder 39.17)
  - May 25, 1980 (Box-folder 39.18)
  - May 26-28, 1980 (Box-folder 39.19)
  - May 29-31, 1980 (Box-folder 39.20)
  - June 1, 1980 (Box-folder 39.21)
  - June 2-4, 1980 (Box-folder 39.22)
  - June 5-6, 1980 (Box-folder 39.23)
  - June 7, 1980 (Box-folder 39.24)
  - June 8, 1980 (Box-folder 39.25)
  - June 9-11, 1980 (Box-folder 39.26)
  - June 12-14, 1980 (Box-folder 39.27)
  - June 15-16, 1980 (Box-folder 39.28)
  - June 17-18, 1980 (Box-folder 39.29)
  - June 19-20, 1980 (Box-folder 39.30)
  - June 21-22, 1980 (Box-folder 40.1)
  - June 23-24, 1980 (Box-folder 40.2)
  - June 25-27, 1980 (Box-folder 40.3)
  - June 28-30, 1980 (Box-folder 40.4)
  - July 1-6, 1980 (Box-folder 40.5)
  - July 7-16, 1980 (Box-folder 40.6)
  - July 17-20, 1980 (Box-folder 40.7)
  - July 22-27, 1980 (Box-folder 40.8)
  - July 28-31, 1980 (Box-folder 40.9)
  - August l, 1980 (Box-folder 40.10)
  - August 2, 1980 (Box-folder 40.11)
  - August 3, 1980 (Box-folder 40.12)
  - August 4, 1980 (Box-folder 40.13)
  - August 5-6, 1980 (Box-folder 40.14)
  - August 7-9, 1980 (Box-folder 40.15)
  - August 10-22, 1980 (Box-folder 40.16)
  - August 13-16, 1980 (Box-folder 40.17)
  - August 17-22, 1980 (Box-folder 40.18)
  - August 23-25, 1980 (Box-folder 40.19)
  - August 26-31, 1980 (Box-folder 40.20)
  - September 2-11, 1980 (Box-folder 40.21)
  - September 12-19, 1980 (Box-folder 40.22)
  - September 20-30, 1980 (Box-folder 40.23)
  - October 1-9, 1980 (Box-folder 40.24)
  - October 10-19, 1980 (Box-folder 40.25)
  - October 20-31, 1980 (Box-folder 40.26)
  - November 1-16, 1980 (Box-folder 40.27)
  - November 17-30, 1980 (Box-folder 40.28)
  - December 1-10, 1980 (Box-folder 41.1)
  - December 11-31, 1980 (Box-folder 41.2)
  - January 1981 (Box-folder 41.3)
  - February 1981 (Box-folder 41.4)
  - May 1981 (Box-folder 41.5)
  - April 1981 (Box-folder 41.6)
  - May 2-26, 1981 (Box-folder 41.7)
  - May 27-31, 1981 (Box-folder 41.8)
  - June 1-14, 1981 (Box-folder 41.9)
  - June 15-30, 1981 (Box-folder 41.10)
  - July 1-8, 1981 (Box-folder 41.11)
  - July 9-31, 1981 (Box-folder 41.12)
  - August 1-9, 1981 (Box-folder 41.13)
  - August 10-31, 1981 (Box-folder 41.14)